{
    "id": "64c2cae4dcd34f87b6693c1903500658",
    "title": "Which word is wrong?",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f09f761b4a04494e981f699a515d87ea",
            "title": "Omission Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have met him a few days ago.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have",
                        "a",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you like some other peas?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "some",
                        "other"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Janet, who is my best friend, she is on holiday at the moment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "she",
                        "the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The baby resembles to its mother.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "the",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The train had left before we reached to the station.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had",
                        "to",
                        "the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was so big a man such that he could not sit in that chair.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Why donâ€™t you think more about others people?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more",
                        "about",
                        "others",
                        "people"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Perhaps you could correct any of mistakes I have made.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "perhaps",
                        "could",
                        "any",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "The life is quite complicated.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "the",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you got a cheaper sort of a camera?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "got",
                        "sort",
                        "a"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}